Mm I think you need a dose of
Vitamin Me
찌는 더위
처진 눈꼬리
잠에 들 것 같은 너
You need some of my citrus
한방울 튄
맘을 담은 squeeze
고장난 네 맘을 touch
You'll be like oh
하나 둘 셋
맘을 refresh
상큼한 Lime juice
I would hate to see you
with a gloomy attitude
원하는 색을 맘대로 섞어
단숨에 들이켜
I'll mix it up
On a silver platter now
Call it Vitamin ME
Imma make you happy
달콤한 Lemon fizz
love it like you do do do do do
Got you feeling new ooh ooh ooh ooh
Imma make you healthy
커져가는 heartbeat
밤이 없는 햇빛 Yes me
Got a boost of Vitamin ME
ME
Not A,B,C
Vitamin ME
ME
Not A,B,C
But you need Vitamin ME
네 하루를 비출 때
미지근한 바람은 부족해
Cause I'm
Feeling you just come alive
I'm the best pick me up
that you ever had
게으른 네 심장을 뛰게해
네가 바라던 노랠 sing along
Like oh
하나 둘 셋 맘을 refresh
새빨간 grapefruit
I would hate to see you
with a gloomy attitude
원하는 색을 맘대로 섞어
단숨에 들이켜
I'll mix it up
On a silver platter now
Call it Vitamin ME
Imma make you happy
달콤한 Lemon fizz
Love it like you do do do do do
Got you feeling new ooh ooh ooh ooh
Imma make you healthy
커져가는 heartbeat
밤이 없는 햇빛 Yes me
Got a boost of Vitamin
ME
Not A,B,C
Vitamin ME
ME
Not A,B,C
But you need Vitamin ME
너만 비추는 spotlight
아무도 몰래 내 손을 잡아
Maybe Maybe you've
Changed Changed me now
너라면 뭐든지 난
한여름의 dreamy
차오르는 sparkling
Love it like you do do do do do
Got you feeling new ooh ooh ooh ooh
싱그러운 wavy
커져가는 heartbeat
밤이 없는 햇빛 Yes me
Got a boost of Vitamin ME
ME
Not A,B,C
Vitamin ME
ME
Not A,B,C
But you need Vitamin ME